newsnshop.in 2013-05-08

# Privacy Policy

**Newsnshop.in Privacy policy:**

**1.** Newsnshop.in respects the private details of users and we promised to keep them safe in our database and will never sell or make them public.  
**2.** Newsnshop.in reserves the rights to change their privacy policy from time to time according to Indian cyber laws and market conditions.  
**3.** This privacy policy explains that how serious we are in keep your information safe and how it is used.  
**4.** We can track and store visitors time, source of request like browser or network and IP address. This all is to make our site more usable and user-friendly for you.  
**5.** We can ask you for some personal information like email, name, mobile number or physical address for signup purpose.  
**6.** We can ask some referrals from you but we reserve the right to store that referral information also.  
**7.** To make your online experience better on our website we can send you newsletters on daily, weekly or monthly basis.

**8.** If you have allowed your browser cookies we can store or track them. Same can be track or store by our affiliates or advertisers also.  
**9.** Signup through on Newsnshop.in through third parties like FaceBook, Twitter, Gmail, Yahoo doesn’t mean we will store your personal or signup information.  
**10.** Our sweepstakes, contests or other promotions through Newsnshop.in may need your registrations with your personal information  
**11.** Entering in any sweepstakes, contests or other promotions means you agree the rules , regulations and terms and conditions of Newsnshop.in  
**12.** We can disclose your information if we need to answer any law enforcement agencies.  
**13.** If you don’t want our newsletters, you can unsubscribe by given link in newsletter.
